https://www.fingerlakeswinecountry.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.fingerlakeswinecountry.com. We understand that online privacy is important to users ("Visitors") and users who register to receive information from us ( "Subscribers") and we have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.
Security
We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Subscribers for any such occurrences.
Data
We may collect basic user profile information or Personally Identifiable Information from all of our Visitors. Personally Identifiable Information refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, or email address. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize and improve the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill information requests (including email newsletters and travel magazines). We may email Visitors and Subscribers about research or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Subscribers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.
What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors, including the following:
Google Analytics: Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.
*Google AdWords: Using cookies to determine past site use, remarketing delivers targeted advertising to users. You can opt-out of receiving these advertisements by using the Consumer Opt-Out process at www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.
*Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting: By serving up the Google Analytics tracking code from the DoubleClick.net advertising network, tracking data on the Site is augmented by key demographic indicators, such as age, gender, and interest, allowing us to further analyze and inform site design, functionality and configuration.
*Not all advanced features and tracking methods are necessarily enabled or configured for this site.
To request information from our organization, Visitors can submit their contact information. The contact information that is collected may include (but is not limited to) first and last name, email address, and mailing address. Requesting to receive information from our organization is done at will, and by doing so you become a “Subscriber.” Subscribers may “opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by us at any time.
Sharing Personally Identifiable Information
When requesting information, if a Subscriber responds yes to sharing their information with our partners to receive additional travel information, their contact information will be shared with our partner organizations. These organizations may use the contact information to send information about their business.
These partner organizations include, but are not limited to, Best Western PLUS The Hammondsport Hotel, Best Western PLUS Vineyard Inn & Suites, Cayuga Lake Wine Trail, Chemung County Chamber of Commerce, Clemens Center, Corning Museum of Glass, Dr. Konstantin Frank Winery, Early Owego Antiques Center, Finger Lakes Distilling, Finger Lakes Premier Properties, Fulkerson Winery, Glenora Wine Cellars, Hampton Inn Horseheads, Hampton Inn Penn Yan, Hazlitt 1852 Vineyards, Hermann J. Wiemer Vineyard, Heron Hill Winery, Hilton Garden Inn Elmira/Corning, Holiday Inn Elmira Riverview, J.R. Dill Winery, Keuka Lake Wine Trail, Lamoreaux Landing Wine Cellars, Pleasant Valley Wine Company, Radisson Hotel Corning, Ravines Wine Cellars, Rockwell Museum, Seneca Lake Wine Trail, Steuben County Conference & Visitors Bureau, Tioga County Tourism, Tioga Downs Casino Resort, Wagner Vineyards, Watkins Glen Area Chamber of Commerce, Watkins Glen Harbor Hotel, Watkins Glen International, and Yates County Chamber of Commerce.
We may share information about our Visitors from Google Analytics, including the demographics and site usage of our Visitors and Subscribers, with our affiliated agencies, third party vendors, board of directors, and partner organizations. We also offer the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.
Storing Personally Identifiable Information
Personally Identifiable Information collected by Finger Lakes Wine Country is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties except for use as indicated above. A number of tools may be used for data collection, including:
Cookies
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. This information helps us to improve our site and the services we provide.
Choices in Collection of Personally Identifiable Information
Visitors and Subsribers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or affiliated agencies and partners. Visitors and Subscribers may delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at:
Finger Lakes Wine Country
1 West Market Street, Suite 203
Corning, NY 14830
800.813.2958 | 607.936.0706
It is possible to opt-out of data collection by using the following resources:
Network Advertisers Initiative Consumer Opt-Out: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
Google Analytics opt-out plugin: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
Policy Modifications & Updates
Finger Lakes Wine Country may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to meet changes in the regulatory environment, business needs, or to satisfy the needs of our Visitors, strategic marketing partners, and service providers.
Login Information
Finger Lakes Wine Country uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.
Partner access to Personally Identifiable Information
Finger Lakes Wine Country has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of businesses and organizations. Such businesses and organizations may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Site performance and audience demographics. Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.
Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to Comply with Law
We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Subscribers.
Links
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
Browse Our Digital Travel Magazine
Sign Up For Our E-Newsletter
Finger Lakes Wine Country Tourism Marketing Association
1 West Market Street, Suite 203
Corning, New York 14830
Subscribe to our Newsletter
About Us
Sitemap
Cookies are used for measurement, ads and optimization. By continuing to use our site you agree to our privacy notice.
Accept
